<resources>
    <string name="app_name">Lesson 3 HW</string>
    <string name="ui_top_message">SWENG Courses</string>
    <string name="return_previous">Return to main activity</string>
    <string name="second_activity_title">Course Info</string>
    <string name="welcome_sweng">PSU Software Engineering</string>
    <string name="show_course_details">Show Course Details</string>

    <string name="sweng888_description">Design and development of mobile computing-based applications and services utilizing current and emerging mobile computing technologies. The purpose of this course is to provide students with an advanced and hands-on exploration of mobile computing paradigms. Mobile computing addresses the mobility needs of business operations and management in organizations, with the increasing trend of leveraging a variety of deployed enterprise information systems. Hence, well-designed and developed mobile applications can meet the needs of business mobility on both the service provider and the customer sides. This course is designed to explore and discuss approaches to the design and development of mobile applications. It builds an awareness of the business need for operational agility and mobility, and the value of existing IT investments in organizations. Specifically, this course investigates the fundamental design and development of mobile applications and services using platform technologies; area topics include mobile application and services design patterns, user interface, animation, location and mapping, and integration. Through working on exercises, labs, and projects, students will be able to identify and apply appropriate mobile platform technologies in their assignments and will gain skills and coding experience in the development of adaptable and sustainable mobile application solutions. Consequently, with this course, students will learn mobile development environments, application and service design and development, device emulators, data and mobility management, and enterprise solution-based integration. Cross Listings: IST 888 will be added as a cross-listed course.</string>
    <string name="sweng894_description">Supervised, professionally oriented student activities that constitute the culminating experience for the program.</string>
    <string name="sweng861_description">Students will learn and practice the elements of constructing a large-scale distributed software system using current technologies. SWENG 861 Software Construction (3) This course will expose the student to the elements and activities of software construction with a particular emphasis in the development of large-scale distributed software systems. Through investigation of large-scale distributed applications, the student will have the knowledge to be much more productive at modern software development. This course will begin by covering the foundation that surrounds large scale software construction such as performance, scalability, fault-tolerance, and security. Following the foundation, a particular emphasis in this course is on technologies that are used to build applications for modern devices and systems as well an emphasis on overcoming the issues that large-scale distributed systems encounter such as security and availability. The student will also investigate web services that help with the interoperability across heterogeneous platforms as well as learn how to handle concurrency, persistence and unit testing across all tiers of the application. Finally, the students will learn how to deal with deployment and security in large-scale distributed systems. Students will learn and practice software construction by developing a project that evolves gracefully as the technology discussion evolves but will have the freedom to work on either Java EE or MS. NET platforms.</string>
    <string name="sweng837_description">The application of engineering best practices to the requirements, analysis and design of large software-centric systems will be presented. This will include the state of the art in software modeling techniques, the Unified Modeling Language and the Unified Process, along with tried and tested structured approaches. Students will learn how to analyze customer requirements and then systematically develop complete software specifications to meet those requirements using appropriate techniques for the application domain.</string>
    <string name="sweng587_description">Software systems architecture; architectural design principles/patterns; documentation/evaluation of software architectures; reuse of architectural assets through frameworks/software product lines. SWENG 587 Software Systems Architecture (3)Architecture is an abstract view of a software system distinct from the details of how such a system is implemented. A robust architecture is key to developing software systems that meet quality expectations (such as performance, scalability, availability, maintainability, etc.) of their stakeholders. This course introduces basic concepts of software architecture, architectural design principles, and patterns. Students also learn how to document and evaluate software architectures, and reuse architectural assets through software product lines. This course is structured to be appropriate for graduate students in software or systems engineering. Many of the topics covered in this course may be applied to a wide variety of research areas. Students will be evaluated on their understanding of the course material by completing one examination (25%), weekly assignments (35%), and an individual project with presentation (40%).</string>
</resources>